nanoleaf.me 2018-10-12

# Nanoleaf Privacy Policy : Nanoleaf.me

**Note that we have introduced a new Terms of Use that will take effect February 1, 2018**. You can find it [here](https://nanoleaf.me/en/terms).

Nanoleaf Canada Ltd. and all its subsidiaries and related companies including Doodle Labs Inc. (collectively “Nanoleaf”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) take privacy seriously. We believe the personal data you share with us should be used for the purpose of working to your benefit. Our ultimate goal when collecting any data is to improve the lives of our customers and help better the environment through technology. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is applicable to our website, eCommerce properties, our mobile applications, and our connected lighting products (“Smarter Series”).

## **SPIRIT OF OUR PRIVACY AND USE OF DATA POLICY**

We use data to improve our products, to personalise content, and to improve the customer service and technical support that we provide to customers. Using data outside of those parameters has no application for our business, and is not of interest to us. It doesn’t matter to us whether you’re John Smith of 123 Main Street or Jane Doe of 789 Front Street. What matters to us is that we continue to get better over time and build things that people love—and that we do right by all of our customers and conduct ourselves in a fair, respectful manner.

We’re opposed to sharing personally-identifiable information with third parties unless it’s with your permission and is strictly relevant to providing you a better experience with our products or services.

## **WHY SHARE YOUR DATA?**

Sharing your personal data with us allows us to improve our products and the service that we offer to you. We may collect personally-identifiable information through the following:

  * Using our connected lighting services including our Smarter Series;
  * Using other connected home services that connect with our Smarter Series;
  * Buying products on The Nanoleaf Shop (with local service in [The Americas](https://us-shop.nanoleaf.me/), [Canada](https://ca-shop.nanoleaf.me/), [Europe / Middle East](https://eu-shop.nanoleaf.me/), [United Kingdom](https://uk-shop.nanoleaf.me/), and [Asia-Pacific](https://int-shop.nanoleaf.me/));
  * Providing you with sales support;
  * Letting you know about the latest and greatest software updates for our products;
  * Improving our website/app through usage statistics;
  * Knowing what products and services are truly important to you.

## **WHAT DATA DO WE COLLECT?**

When you connect your Nanoleaf Smarter Series devices to Nanoleaf’s servers, we collect event data based on direct interactions with your devices. This includes:

  * Turning lights on and off
  * Adjusting brightness
  * Settings Scenes
  * Setting colors

This data is fed into Nanoleaf’s algorithms and analysis tools and is used to provide you access to advanced features and product enhancements.

Our mobile apps collect anonymized usage data on how the app is used. This data is used for the purposes of enhancing the mobile app experience. You may choose to share content with the Nanoleaf Community through our mobile Apps. This content is collected and stored once submitted.

Our website collects information to help us understand our customers and create the best experience possible. This data includes things like your IP address, cookie ID, web browser, location, and pages you visit on our website. Our website uses a number of analysis services to help us identify patterns of behaviour, offer personalised content, and improve our products. We do not collect personally-identifiable information from these services; however, they may collect information that they do not share with us in accordance with their own privacy policies.

These analytical services include:

  * Google Analytics (including Remarketing)
  * Google Tag Manager
  * Google Optimize
  * DoubleClick by Google
  * Facebook Connect
  * Twitter Connect
  * Snapchat Analytics

For further information on privacy and data handling, please refer to:

When purchasing items from the Nanoleaf Shop, you voluntarily give us your name, email address, payment information, billing and shipping addresses, and telephone number. We use this information solely for processing your order. If you have opted-in to receive marketing communications from us, we will send you promotional offers from time to time. You may unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any message. This prevents any promotional emails from being sent to you unless you explicitly request that we re-add you to a promotional list.

## **Our Use of Cookies and Log Files**

We use browser tracking cookies (or “cookies”), which are small text files that are placed on the hard disk of a computer by a website. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a website or web server that issued the cookie to you. We also use browser “log files” which record certain information when you visit a website, including your internet protocol (IP) address.

We use cookies and logs files to improve your experience on our Website, such as to recognize you when you return to our website; keep track of activity on our Website and remember what items you have clicked on or viewed; study how you navigate through our website and which products you request in site searches so that we can improve the design, content and function of our Website; and customize the message, content and delivery of online banner advertisements and e-mails that reflect how you navigate to and through our Website based on your online behavior. We call this “Browsing Data”.

We may hire third-party service providers to assist us in the collection and analysis of this Browsing Data collected through cookies, but none of your personal information is disclosed to these third party service providers.

You have the ability to accept or decline our use of cookies. You can refuse cookies by turning them off or blocking them in your internet browser. If you decide to turn off or block cookies, our website might not function correctly.

## **WHERE IS YOUR DATA KEPT?**

We take reasonable precautions to protect your personal data. Personally-identifiable information provided along with any purchases made through our store is encrypted using SSL and stored with AES-256 encryption. The Nanoleaf Shop is hosted by Shopify. For more information on Shopify’s data-handling practices, please read Shopify’s Terms of Service (<https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms>) and Privacy Statement (<https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy>). The Nanoleaf Perks loyalty program is administered by Smile.io. You may wish to refer to their Privacy Policy for further information (<https://smile.io/privacy-policy>).

Our Smarter Series also uses the latest in encryption technology to communicate using HomeKit and ZigBee.

## **HOW DOES NANOLEAF INTERACT WITH THIRD PARTIES?**

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties, except if, and to the extent necessary, in our good faith judgment, doing so is required: by law, for the transactional needs of facilitating eCommerce orders, for administering the Nanoleaf Perks program, or where you have given explicit consent.

We may share your data with third party services like Amazon Alexa, Google Assistant, IFTTT and others when you choose to connect your Nanoleaf Account with these services. In all cases, our service will ask for your permission before actually sharing information. These sites operate independently of us and have established their own privacy and security policies. Any personal information you choose to share with third parties is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. We encourage you to review these policies at any site you visit. This Policy does not apply to such linked pages or other sites, and we are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked websites that are provided solely for your convenience.

## **PARENTAL INFORMATION**

While we design our products to be simple enough for use by all family members, we do not specifically target our products toward children under the age of 13. We do not intend to collect personal information on minors under the age of 13 and we encourage parents and guardians to supervise how children are sharing information online. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will make commercially reasonably efforts to delete such personal information from our database.

## **Your Decisions About Your Personal Information**

You may stop receiving emails from us by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any message. This prevents any promotional emails from being sent to you unless you explicitly request that we re-add you to a promotional list.

If you would like to review the personal information held by us in connection with your account; withdraw your consent for our use and disclosure of your information; request a list of third parties to which the Company may have provided your personal information; or amend your personal information, where possible, you can contact us at [hello@nanoleaf.me](mailto:hello@nanoleaf.me).

If you would like to close your account, you can contact us at [accounts@nanoleaf.me](mailto:accounts@nanoleaf.me).

If you contact us to do any of the things listed above, we may require you to provide sufficient personal information to allow us to identify you and tell you about the existence, use and disclosure of your personal information and this personal information will only be used for this purpose. If you contact us about your personal information, we will respond to your request within a reasonable time and at no cost to you.

## Clarifications Relevant to EU Directive 2016/679 (“General Data Protection Regulation”)

Our current privacy policy and terms of service are aligned with the spirit of the GDPR. You may, at any time, request amendments to your personal information or deletion of your personal data (‘the right to be forgotten’) from our records by emailing accounts@nanoleaf.me. We commit to addressing these requests within a reasonable time frame (our goal is resolution within one week of receiving a request).

## **QUESTIONS? CONTACT US.**

If you have any other inquiries, including questions about this Policy, please email us at [hello@nanoleaf.me](mailto:hello@nanoleaf.me).

## **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We are always looking to serve our customers better and as a result we anticipate that this policy will need to be updated as we evolve. In serving you better, we reserve the right to change this policy occasionally. We will make reasonable efforts to update you on items relevant to you.

Posted Date: December 7, 2017.

Effective Date: February 1, 2018.

_Amended March 29, 2018 to provide clarifications relevant to GDPR in the European Union._

**Note that we have introduced a new Terms of Use that will take effect February 1, 2018**. You can find it [here](https://nanoleaf.me/en/terms).

Nanoleaf Canada Ltd. and all its subsidiaries and related companies including Doodle Labs Inc. (collectively “Nanoleaf”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) take privacy seriously. We believe the personal data you share with us should be used for the purpose of working to your benefit. Our ultimate goal when collecting any data is to improve the lives of our customers and help better the environment through technology. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is applicable to our website, eCommerce properties, our mobile applications, and our connected lighting products (“Smarter Series”).

## **SPIRIT OF OUR PRIVACY AND USE OF DATA POLICY**

We use data to improve our products, to personalise content, and to improve the customer service and technical support that we provide to customers. Using data outside of those parameters has no application for our business, and is not of interest to us. It doesn’t matter to us whether you’re John Smith of 123 Main Street or Jane Doe of 789 Front Street. What matters to us is that we continue to get better over time and build things that people love—and that we do right by all of our customers and conduct ourselves in a fair, respectful manner.

We’re opposed to sharing personally-identifiable information with third parties unless it’s with your permission and is strictly relevant to providing you a better experience with our products or services.

## **WHY SHARE YOUR DATA?**

Sharing your personal data with us allows us to improve our products and the service that we offer to you. We may collect personally-identifiable information through the following:

  * Using our connected lighting services including our Smarter Series;
  * Using other connected home services that connect with our Smarter Series;
  * Buying products on The Nanoleaf Shop (with local service in [The Americas](https://us-shop.nanoleaf.me/), [Canada](https://ca-shop.nanoleaf.me/), [Europe / Middle East](https://eu-shop.nanoleaf.me/), [United Kingdom](https://uk-shop.nanoleaf.me/), and [Asia-Pacific](https://int-shop.nanoleaf.me/));
  * Providing you with sales support;
  * Letting you know about the latest and greatest software updates for our products;
  * Improving our website/app through usage statistics;
  * Knowing what products and services are truly important to you.

## **WHAT DATA DO WE COLLECT?**

When you connect your Nanoleaf Smarter Series devices to Nanoleaf’s servers, we collect event data based on direct interactions with your devices. This includes:

  * Turning lights on and off
  * Adjusting brightness
  * Settings Scenes
  * Setting colors

This data is fed into Nanoleaf’s algorithms and analysis tools and is used to provide you access to advanced features and product enhancements.

Our mobile apps collect anonymized usage data on how the app is used. This data is used for the purposes of enhancing the mobile app experience. You may choose to share content with the Nanoleaf Community through our mobile Apps. This content is collected and stored once submitted.

Our website collects information to help us understand our customers and create the best experience possible. This data includes things like your IP address, cookie ID, web browser, location, and pages you visit on our website. Our website uses a number of analysis services to help us identify patterns of behaviour, offer personalised content, and improve our products. We do not collect personally-identifiable information from these services; however, they may collect information that they do not share with us in accordance with their own privacy policies.

These analytical services include:

  * Google Analytics (including Remarketing)
  * Google Tag Manager
  * Google Optimize
  * DoubleClick by Google
  * Facebook Connect
  * Twitter Connect
  * Snapchat Analytics

For further information on privacy and data handling, please refer to:

When purchasing items from the Nanoleaf Shop, you voluntarily give us your name, email address, payment information, billing and shipping addresses, and telephone number. We use this information solely for processing your order. If you have opted-in to receive marketing communications from us, we will send you promotional offers from time to time. You may unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any message. This prevents any promotional emails from being sent to you unless you explicitly request that we re-add you to a promotional list.

## **Our Use of Cookies and Log Files**

We use browser tracking cookies (or “cookies”), which are small text files that are placed on the hard disk of a computer by a website. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a website or web server that issued the cookie to you. We also use browser “log files” which record certain information when you visit a website, including your internet protocol (IP) address.

We use cookies and logs files to improve your experience on our Website, such as to recognize you when you return to our website; keep track of activity on our Website and remember what items you have clicked on or viewed; study how you navigate through our website and which products you request in site searches so that we can improve the design, content and function of our Website; and customize the message, content and delivery of online banner advertisements and e-mails that reflect how you navigate to and through our Website based on your online behavior. We call this “Browsing Data”.

We may hire third-party service providers to assist us in the collection and analysis of this Browsing Data collected through cookies, but none of your personal information is disclosed to these third party service providers.

You have the ability to accept or decline our use of cookies. You can refuse cookies by turning them off or blocking them in your internet browser. If you decide to turn off or block cookies, our website might not function correctly.

## **WHERE IS YOUR DATA KEPT?**

We take reasonable precautions to protect your personal data. Personally-identifiable information provided along with any purchases made through our store is encrypted using SSL and stored with AES-256 encryption. The Nanoleaf Shop is hosted by Shopify. For more information on Shopify’s data-handling practices, please read Shopify’s Terms of Service (<https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms>) and Privacy Statement (<https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy>). The Nanoleaf Perks loyalty program is administered by Smile.io. You may wish to refer to their Privacy Policy for further information (<https://smile.io/privacy-policy>).

Our Smarter Series also uses the latest in encryption technology to communicate using HomeKit and ZigBee.

## **HOW DOES NANOLEAF INTERACT WITH THIRD PARTIES?**

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties, except if, and to the extent necessary, in our good faith judgment, doing so is required: by law, for the transactional needs of facilitating eCommerce orders, for administering the Nanoleaf Perks program, or where you have given explicit consent.

We may share your data with third party services like Amazon Alexa, Google Assistant, IFTTT and others when you choose to connect your Nanoleaf Account with these services. In all cases, our service will ask for your permission before actually sharing information. These sites operate independently of us and have established their own privacy and security policies. Any personal information you choose to share with third parties is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. We encourage you to review these policies at any site you visit. This Policy does not apply to such linked pages or other sites, and we are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked websites that are provided solely for your convenience.

## **PARENTAL INFORMATION**

While we design our products to be simple enough for use by all family members, we do not specifically target our products toward children under the age of 13. We do not intend to collect personal information on minors under the age of 13 and we encourage parents and guardians to supervise how children are sharing information online. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will make commercially reasonably efforts to delete such personal information from our database.

## **Your Decisions About Your Personal Information**

You may stop receiving emails from us by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any message. This prevents any promotional emails from being sent to you unless you explicitly request that we re-add you to a promotional list.

If you would like to review the personal information held by us in connection with your account; withdraw your consent for our use and disclosure of your information; request a list of third parties to which the Company may have provided your personal information; or amend your personal information, where possible, you can contact us at [hello@nanoleaf.me](mailto:hello@nanoleaf.me).

If you would like to close your account, you can contact us at [accounts@nanoleaf.me](mailto:accounts@nanoleaf.me).

If you contact us to do any of the things listed above, we may require you to provide sufficient personal information to allow us to identify you and tell you about the existence, use and disclosure of your personal information and this personal information will only be used for this purpose. If you contact us about your personal information, we will respond to your request within a reasonable time and at no cost to you.

## Clarifications Relevant to EU Directive 2016/679 (“General Data Protection Regulation”)

Our current privacy policy and terms of service are aligned with the spirit of the GDPR. You may, at any time, request amendments to your personal information or deletion of your personal data (‘the right to be forgotten’) from our records by emailing accounts@nanoleaf.me. We commit to addressing these requests within a reasonable time frame (our goal is resolution within one week of receiving a request).

## **QUESTIONS? CONTACT US.**

If you have any other inquiries, including questions about this Policy, please email us at [hello@nanoleaf.me](mailto:hello@nanoleaf.me).

## **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We are always looking to serve our customers better and as a result we anticipate that this policy will need to be updated as we evolve. In serving you better, we reserve the right to change this policy occasionally. We will make reasonable efforts to update you on items relevant to you.

Posted Date: December 7, 2017.

Effective Date: February 1, 2018.

_Amended March 29, 2018 to provide clarifications relevant to GDPR in the European Union._

**Note that we have introduced a new Terms of Use that will take effect February 1, 2018**. You can find it [here](https://nanoleaf.me/en/terms).

Nanoleaf Canada Ltd. and all its subsidiaries and related companies including Doodle Labs Inc. (collectively “Nanoleaf”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) take privacy seriously. We believe the personal data you share with us should be used for the purpose of working to your benefit. Our ultimate goal when collecting any data is to improve the lives of our customers and help better the environment through technology. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is applicable to our website, eCommerce properties, our mobile applications, and our connected lighting products (“Smarter Series”).

## **SPIRIT OF OUR PRIVACY AND USE OF DATA POLICY**

We use data to improve our products, to personalise content, and to improve the customer service and technical support that we provide to customers. Using data outside of those parameters has no application for our business, and is not of interest to us. It doesn’t matter to us whether you’re John Smith of 123 Main Street or Jane Doe of 789 Front Street. What matters to us is that we continue to get better over time and build things that people love—and that we do right by all of our customers and conduct ourselves in a fair, respectful manner.

We’re opposed to sharing personally-identifiable information with third parties unless it’s with your permission and is strictly relevant to providing you a better experience with our products or services.

## **WHY SHARE YOUR DATA?**

Sharing your personal data with us allows us to improve our products and the service that we offer to you. We may collect personally-identifiable information through the following:

  * Using our connected lighting services including our Smarter Series;
  * Using other connected home services that connect with our Smarter Series;
  * Buying products on The Nanoleaf Shop (with local service in [The Americas](https://us-shop.nanoleaf.me/), [Canada](https://ca-shop.nanoleaf.me/), [Europe / Middle East](https://eu-shop.nanoleaf.me/), [United Kingdom](https://uk-shop.nanoleaf.me/), and [Asia-Pacific](https://int-shop.nanoleaf.me/));
  * Providing you with sales support;
  * Letting you know about the latest and greatest software updates for our products;
  * Improving our website/app through usage statistics;
  * Knowing what products and services are truly important to you.

## **WHAT DATA DO WE COLLECT?**

When you connect your Nanoleaf Smarter Series devices to Nanoleaf’s servers, we collect event data based on direct interactions with your devices. This includes:

  * Turning lights on and off
  * Adjusting brightness
  * Settings Scenes
  * Setting colors

This data is fed into Nanoleaf’s algorithms and analysis tools and is used to provide you access to advanced features and product enhancements.

Our mobile apps collect anonymized usage data on how the app is used. This data is used for the purposes of enhancing the mobile app experience. You may choose to share content with the Nanoleaf Community through our mobile Apps. This content is collected and stored once submitted.

Our website collects information to help us understand our customers and create the best experience possible. This data includes things like your IP address, cookie ID, web browser, location, and pages you visit on our website. Our website uses a number of analysis services to help us identify patterns of behaviour, offer personalised content, and improve our products. We do not collect personally-identifiable information from these services; however, they may collect information that they do not share with us in accordance with their own privacy policies.

These analytical services include:

  * Google Analytics (including Remarketing)
  * Google Tag Manager
  * Google Optimize
  * DoubleClick by Google
  * Facebook Connect
  * Twitter Connect
  * Snapchat Analytics

For further information on privacy and data handling, please refer to:

When purchasing items from the Nanoleaf Shop, you voluntarily give us your name, email address, payment information, billing and shipping addresses, and telephone number. We use this information solely for processing your order. If you have opted-in to receive marketing communications from us, we will send you promotional offers from time to time. You may unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any message. This prevents any promotional emails from being sent to you unless you explicitly request that we re-add you to a promotional list.

## **Our Use of Cookies and Log Files**

We use browser tracking cookies (or “cookies”), which are small text files that are placed on the hard disk of a computer by a website. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a website or web server that issued the cookie to you. We also use browser “log files” which record certain information when you visit a website, including your internet protocol (IP) address.

We use cookies and logs files to improve your experience on our Website, such as to recognize you when you return to our website; keep track of activity on our Website and remember what items you have clicked on or viewed; study how you navigate through our website and which products you request in site searches so that we can improve the design, content and function of our Website; and customize the message, content and delivery of online banner advertisements and e-mails that reflect how you navigate to and through our Website based on your online behavior. We call this “Browsing Data”.

We may hire third-party service providers to assist us in the collection and analysis of this Browsing Data collected through cookies, but none of your personal information is disclosed to these third party service providers.

You have the ability to accept or decline our use of cookies. You can refuse cookies by turning them off or blocking them in your internet browser. If you decide to turn off or block cookies, our website might not function correctly.

## **WHERE IS YOUR DATA KEPT?**

We take reasonable precautions to protect your personal data. Personally-identifiable information provided along with any purchases made through our store is encrypted using SSL and stored with AES-256 encryption. The Nanoleaf Shop is hosted by Shopify. For more information on Shopify’s data-handling practices, please read Shopify’s Terms of Service (<https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms>) and Privacy Statement (<https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy>). The Nanoleaf Perks loyalty program is administered by Smile.io. You may wish to refer to their Privacy Policy for further information (<https://smile.io/privacy-policy>).

Our Smarter Series also uses the latest in encryption technology to communicate using HomeKit and ZigBee.

## **HOW DOES NANOLEAF INTERACT WITH THIRD PARTIES?**

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties, except if, and to the extent necessary, in our good faith judgment, doing so is required: by law, for the transactional needs of facilitating eCommerce orders, for administering the Nanoleaf Perks program, or where you have given explicit consent.

We may share your data with third party services like Amazon Alexa, Google Assistant, IFTTT and others when you choose to connect your Nanoleaf Account with these services. In all cases, our service will ask for your permission before actually sharing information. These sites operate independently of us and have established their own privacy and security policies. Any personal information you choose to share with third parties is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. We encourage you to review these policies at any site you visit. This Policy does not apply to such linked pages or other sites, and we are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked websites that are provided solely for your convenience.

## **PARENTAL INFORMATION**

While we design our products to be simple enough for use by all family members, we do not specifically target our products toward children under the age of 13. We do not intend to collect personal information on minors under the age of 13 and we encourage parents and guardians to supervise how children are sharing information online. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will make commercially reasonably efforts to delete such personal information from our database.

## **Your Decisions About Your Personal Information**

You may stop receiving emails from us by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any message. This prevents any promotional emails from being sent to you unless you explicitly request that we re-add you to a promotional list.

If you would like to review the personal information held by us in connection with your account; withdraw your consent for our use and disclosure of your information; request a list of third parties to which the Company may have provided your personal information; or amend your personal information, where possible, you can contact us at [hello@nanoleaf.me](mailto:hello@nanoleaf.me).

If you would like to close your account, you can contact us at [accounts@nanoleaf.me](mailto:accounts@nanoleaf.me).

If you contact us to do any of the things listed above, we may require you to provide sufficient personal information to allow us to identify you and tell you about the existence, use and disclosure of your personal information and this personal information will only be used for this purpose. If you contact us about your personal information, we will respond to your request within a reasonable time and at no cost to you.

## Clarifications Relevant to EU Directive 2016/679 (“General Data Protection Regulation”)

Our current privacy policy and terms of service are aligned with the spirit of the GDPR. You may, at any time, request amendments to your personal information or deletion of your personal data (‘the right to be forgotten’) from our records by emailing accounts@nanoleaf.me. We commit to addressing these requests within a reasonable time frame (our goal is resolution within one week of receiving a request).

## **QUESTIONS? CONTACT US.**

If you have any other inquiries, including questions about this Policy, please email us at [hello@nanoleaf.me](mailto:hello@nanoleaf.me).

## **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We are always looking to serve our customers better and as a result we anticipate that this policy will need to be updated as we evolve. In serving you better, we reserve the right to change this policy occasionally. We will make reasonable efforts to update you on items relevant to you.

Posted Date: December 7, 2017.

Effective Date: February 1, 2018.

_Amended March 29, 2018 to provide clarifications relevant to GDPR in the European Union._
